[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：你说我们做一些面向对象的编程？
&gt;&gt; Douglas: When you say we do some object-oriented programming?
好的。
Yeah, all right.
是啊。
Yeah.
所以我们现在要对一个物体做些什么。
So we're gonna do something with an object now.
我们将编写一个计数器函数，它返回一个包含两个函数的对象
We're gonna write a counter function that returns an object containing two functions
它实现了一个向上向下的计数器，隐藏了计数器。
that implement an up down counter, hiding the counter.
所以我们将调用计数器工厂并传入一个初始值，
So we'll call the counter factory and pass in an initial value,
它将返回一个包含up方法和down方法的对象，并且
and it will return an object containing an up method and a down method, and
当我们调用时，它将向值中加1并返回它。
when we call up, it will add one to the value and return it.
当我们向下调用时，它将从值中减去1
When we call down, it will subtract one from the value and
还给我。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：和
return it. &gt;&gt; Douglas: And
我给你个提示，没有全局变量。
I'll give you a hint, no global variables.
不是这个，不是那些废话。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：我们不需要这些。
No this, none of that crap. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We don't need any of that.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：该死。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Darn it.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：我总是使用global
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I always use global
变数无处不在。
variables everywhere.
这是Ben教我做的。&gt；&gt；演讲者3：我没有教你怎么做
It's what Ben taught me to do. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: I did not teach you to do
那个。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：什么能去-本总是
that. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: What could go- Ben always
说更多的全球信息。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：正好相反
says more globals. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: It's exactly the opposite of
那个。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：更多
that. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: More
全球。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：这里是计数器，
globals. &gt;&gt; Douglas: So here is counter,
它接受一个值，它返回一个包含两个函数的对象。
it takes a value, it returns an object containing two functions.
第一个是up函数，它将值加1并返回。
The first one, the up function, adds one to the value and returns it.
另一个，向下功能，
The other one, the down function,
从值中减去1并返回它。
subtracts one from the value and returns it.
那么谁有用的东西呢？
So who got something that works?
才华横溢。
Brilliant.
如果你没有得到它，写下来，
If you didn't get it, write it down,
因为你以后会想参考这个模式。
cuz you'll want to refer to this pattern later.
所以这与我们昨天讨论的非常相似，我们得到了
So this is very similar to what we talked about yesterday, where we've got
闭包中的两个函数都共享公共数据。
two functions inside of a closure which are both sharing common data.
这是一个非常简单的例子，但是
This is a very simple example of that, but
基本上，所有对象构造函数都将遵循此模式。
basically, all object constructors are gonna follow this pattern.
关于这个有什么问题吗？
Any questions about this?
好的，想再做一个吗？
Okay, want to do another one?
所以下一个，我保证，
So this next one, I promise,
听起来会比实际情况更糟，好吗？
is going to sound much worse than it actually is, okay?
因此，创建一个可撤销的函数，它接受一个二进制函数并
So, make a revocable function that takes a binary function and
返回一个包含Invoke函数的对象，该函数可以调用二进制文件
returns an object containing an invoke function that can invoke the binary
函数和禁用Invoke函数的REVOKE函数。
function and a revoke function that disables the invoke function.
好的，让我来解释一下这里到底发生了什么。
Okay, so let me explain what's actually going on here.
这可能具有一些安全属性，并且我们可能
This is something that might have some security properties, and that we might
有一些客户代码，我们允许进入我们的系统，我们希望它能够
have some guest code that we allow into our system, and we want it to be able to
我们想跑多久就跑多久，但在任何时候，我们都希望能够切断它。
run as long as we want it to, but at any point, we want to be able to cut it off.
我们不想为了实现以下目的而重写现有的API
And we don't want to have to rewrite our existing APIs in order to
适应这一点。
accommodate that.
这是我们之前写的极限函数的一个变体。
So this is a variation on the limit function that we wrote earlier.
实际上，当您正在执行以下操作时，您可能希望参考您的Limit实现
In fact, you might want to refer to your implementation of limit when you're
做这个。
doing this one.
除了这一个，而不是统计你要做多少次
Except in this one, instead of keeping a count about how many times you get to do
它，我们将有一个名为revoke的单独函数，它将，
it, we will have a separate function called revoke, which will,
当我们调用它时，使它停止工作。
when we call it, cause the thing to stop working.
好的，所以我们将调用可撤销的工厂，我们将传入任何现有的函数，在
Okay, so we'll call our revocable factory, we'll pass in any existing function, in
本例中为add函数，它将返回一个包含两个函数的对象。
this case, the add function, and it will return an object containing two functions.
其中之一将是Invoke函数，它是可撤销的Add函数。
One of them will be the invoke function, which is the revocable add function.
我们可以把这个功能交给第三方，但是
And we can give that function to the third party, but
我们将为自己保留REVOKE函数。
we will hold on to the revoke function for ourselves.
因此，可撤销的add函数将像add一样工作，直到
So the revocable add function will work just like add until
我们调用revoke函数。
we call the revoke function.
在这一点上，它所做的就是返回undefined。
At that point, all it does is return undefined.
大家都清楚了吗？&gt；&gt；扬声器2：所以
Everybody clear? &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So
基本上，我们真正需要的是点参数和
it's basically, what we really need, the dot dot dot arguments and
然后[INAUDIBLE]。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：是的，我们希望这能起作用
then [INAUDIBLE]. &gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah, we want this to work for
所有功能，对吗？&gt；&gt；扬声器2：是的，并且
all functions, right? &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, and
这只适用于。&gt；&gt；Douglas：用于二进制。
that only works for. &gt;&gt; Douglas: For binary.
实际上，任何适用于二进制的东西，可能都适用于一元，
And actually, anything that works for binary, probably works for unary,
因为我们只是将undefined作为第二个参数传递，
because we're just gonna pass undefined as the second argument,
然后它就被忽略了。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：SO
then it gets ignored. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So
[听不见]可以提前计划&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：是的，如果你知道我们从来没有
[INAUDIBLE] could just plan ahead. &gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah, if you knew we never
使用了十多台路由器，您可以做到这一点，但谁愿意这样做呢？
used more than ten routers, you could do that, but who wants to do that?
是的，很可怕。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：但是
Yeah, it's awful. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: But
你可以打电话，如果在里面，你可以随时打电话给我们的
you could call, if inside, you could always just call our
[听不见]你可以把它传到任何地方？&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：你
[INAUDIBLE] you can pass that wherever? &gt;&gt; Douglas: You
可以。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：好的。
can. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Okay.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：所以你今天可以这样做，
&gt;&gt; Douglas: So you can do that today,
太难看了，我不想浪费你的时间，所以
it's just inexcusably ugly, and I don't want to waste your time with it, so
我们不会那么做的。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：[无法听到]参数为零，
we're not gonna do that. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [INAUDIBLE] Argument zero,
参数一，参数二，你不能直接传入参数对象。
argument one, argument two, you can't just pass in the arguments object.
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：实际上，你不能，是的，
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Actually, you can't, yeah,
这是个问题&gt；&gt；扬声器2：它不起作用
which is kind of a problem. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It didn't work for
我就是那样。
me that way.
那是我去的地方，
That was my go to,
尝试那个[INAUDIBLE]好。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：你可能
to try that [INAUDIBLE] Good. &gt;&gt; Douglas: You probably
做错了什么，这很好。
did something wrong, which is great.
&gt；&gt；[笑]&gt；&gt；Douglas：继续做
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Douglas: Keep doing
那个。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：它是
that. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: It's
争论？&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：争论。
arguments? &gt;&gt; Douglas: Arguments.
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：所以如果你在
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So if you get arguments in
一个函数，然后调用其中的另一个函数，传递参数，
a function, and you call another function inside of that, passing arguments,
您将数组传递给该函数，而不是传递
you're passing an array to that function, you're not passing
该数组中的每个参数。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：对。
each of the arguments in that array. &gt;&gt; Douglas: Right.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：这就是为什么它不起作用。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: That's why it doesn't work.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：但然后可以使用Apply
&gt;&gt; Douglas: But you could then use apply
把它展开。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：在ES6或？
to spread it out. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: In ES6 or?
&gt；&gt；Douglas：在ES3中。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: In ES3.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Okay.
道格拉斯：是的。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：阵列。应用[INAUDIBLE]。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Array.apply [INAUDIBLE].
对不起，[INAUDIBLE]争论。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：不，不幸的是，
I'm sorry, [INAUDIBLE] arguments. &gt;&gt; Douglas: No, unfortunately,
这是函数应用。
it's Function.apply.
所以，我们不会这么做。
So, we're not doing that.
太可怕了。&GT；&GT；扬声器3：对，
It's too awful. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: That's right,
你昨天给我们看了。
you showed us yesterday.
你说它很丑，所以我忽略了它。道格拉斯：是的，
And you said it was ugly, so I ignored it. &gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah,
很好你忽略了它。
it was good that you ignored it.
好的，我们准备好撤销了吗？
Okay, we ready for revocable?
所以这里是可撤销的。
So here's revocable.
它接受一个二进制函数并返回一个包含Invoke方法和
It takes a binary function and returns an object containing an invoke method and
REVOKE方法。
a revoke method.
Invoke方法查看是否未定义二进制。
The invoke method looks to see if binary is undefined.
如果不是，那么它将调用它，传递第一个和第二个参数。
If it isn't, then it will call it, passing the first and second argument.
否则，它不做任何事情并返回undefined。
Otherwise, it doesn't do anything and returns undefined.
REVOKE函数将BINARY设置为UNDEFINED，从而禁用Invoke函数。
Revoke function sets binary to undefined, thereby disabling the invoke function.
那么谁有用的东西呢？
So who's got something that works?
非常好。
Very good.
有人做了什么不同的事吗？
Anybody do something different?
有什么值得注意的吗？&gt；&gt；扬声器3：我放了一个变量好的，哪一个
Something notable? &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: I put a variable okay which
我设置为FALSE，但都是一样的。&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：没关系，
I set to false, but it's the same thing. &gt;&gt; Douglas: That is okay,
是啊。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：谢谢。
yeah. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Thanks.
所以，我打开这个，所以我创造了。
So, I open this up, so I create.
我们制作了这个物体，它在，
We made this object, which is in the,
我在控制台中看着我的对象，我想反省它。
and I look in the console at my object, and I want to introspect it.
所以我扩展了它。
So I expand it.
二进制在哪里？
Where's binary in there?
很明显，它不是作为这个对象的一部分公开的，
It's obvious, it's not exposed publicly as a part of this object,
但它知道这件事。道格拉斯：对，
but it knows about it. &gt;&gt; Douglas: Right,
二进制隐藏在可撤销函数的函数作用域中，并且
binary is hidden in the function scope of the revocable function, and
只有在其关闭时才可用。
is available only through its closure.
并且宇宙中唯一可以访问该闭包的函数被调用，并且
And the only functions in the universe who have access to that closure are invoke and
撤销。
revoke.
所以这就是为什么我们可以用它来构建安全系统的原因。
So that's why this is something that we can build secure systems out of.
你知道，如果我们拿走你的OK旗帜
You know, if we were to take your okay flag and
将其放在对象本身中，然后攻击者可以进入该对象并
put it in the object itself, then the attacker could go to the object and
把它转到另一个方向。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：好的。
turn it the other way. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Right.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：所以这不会实现
&gt;&gt; Douglas: So that wouldn't accomplish
我们想在这里做什么。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：SO
what we want to do here. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So
我们显然可以查看来源，但你显然会，我的意思是，它是。
we could obviously look at the source, but you'd obviously, I mean, it's.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：对，所以
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Right, so
我们假设攻击者总是可以查看源代码。
we assume that the attacker can always look at the source.
但是他们可以看看这个消息来源，这对他们没有帮助，对吧，
But they can look at this source and it doesn't help them, right,
除非他们在创建对象时在场，否则他们无法到达它。
unless they were there at the creation of the object, they can't get to it.
他们不能进入二进制。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：SO
They can't get to binary. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So
在这种情况下，撤销是不可撤销的。&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：没错，
revoke is irrevocable in this case. &gt;&gt; Douglas: That's right,
这是单程旅行。
this is a one-way trip.
现在，我们可以设计这个以不同的方式工作。
Now, we could design this to work a different way.
使用他的OK变量作为开关，我们可以提供第二个
Using his okay variable as an on-off switch, we could provide a second
函数或者可能是要撤销的参数，可以将其逆转。
function or maybe an argument to revoke which could reverse it.
但一般来说，我更喜欢这样的系统，一旦我们切断它们，它就会被切断，而我们不会
But generally, I prefer systems where once we cut them off, it's off, and we don't
必须担心有什么东西以一种意想不到的方式再次打开它。
have to worry about something turning it back on again in an unexpected way.
是吗？&gt；&gt；扬声器4：因为你没有明确
Yeah? &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Since you're not explicitly
返回Invoke中未定义的？&gt；&gt；Douglas：mm-hm。
returning undefined in the invoke? &gt;&gt; Douglas: Mm-hm.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：这是不是你
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Is this a case where you
说，你在是否应该返回未定义或
said, you flip flop on whether you should return undefined or
不是吗？&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：没错。
not? &gt;&gt; Douglas: That's right.
我的意思是，我喜欢，直截了当的想法，我也不喜欢
I mean, I like, the idea of being explicit, and I also like not
做我不需要做的事。&gt；&gt；[笑]。
doing anything I don't have to do. &gt;&gt; [LAUGH].
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：有点不一致
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Kind of at odds with each
其他。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：是的，没错。
other. &gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah, exactly.
那里有一个真正的冲突。
There's a real conflict there.
但大多数时候，做正确的事情
But most of the time, doing the right thing and
做正确的事显然是一回事。
doing the right thing are obviously the same thing.
这是其中一种情况，它不是那么多。
This is one of the cases where it isn't so much.